Guide to the George Dix Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
George Dix papers
1946-1992
GEN MSS 403
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
3.5
(8 boxes)
Collection consists of working files maintained by George Dix, primarily during his partnership with R. Kirk Askew at Durlacher Bros. The files contain correspondence, biographical information, exhibition catalogs, photographs, and other papers related to artists represented by the gallery, as well as papers concerning exhibitions of older artists, such as Edward Lear and Joseph Wright of Derby. Artists represented in the files include Peter Blume, Barbara Hepworth, Robin Ironside, Leonid, Ben Nicholson, Marjorie Phillips, and John Piper.
Dix, George
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of George Dix (Yale class of 1934), 1997.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 8: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
In 1948, already established as an art dealer, George Dix began his partnership with R. Kirk Askew at the New York gallery of Durlacher Bros., where he handled the British painters represented by the gallery. After 124 years of business, Durlacher Bros. closed in 1967. Dix, having worked for many years with contemporary artists, made plans to open a gallery in his own name, concentrating on old master drawings and paintings.
Scope and Contents
The George Dix Papers contain correspondence, exhibition catalogs, photographs, notes and other papers that document the work of George Dix. The Papers have been arranged into two series, Series I, Durlacher Bros. Files and Series II, Artists Files. The papers span the years 1946-1992.
Series I, Durlacher Bros. Files, contains general files detailing the workings of the gallery, including correspondence, subject files, and photographs. The correspondence consists of letters by George Dix, R. Kirk Askew, Princeton University Dept. of Art and Archaeology, and others. The letters from R. Kirk Askew concern Dix's partnership with Durlacher Bros. The subject files contain exhibition catalogs and other papers. The photographs consist of works by painters, divided into works for sale, works sold, and other categories.
Series II, Artists Files, contains the subject files George Dix kept on artists he represented on behalf of Durlacher Bros., or in the case Edward Lear and Joseph Wright of Derby, artists for whom special exhibitions were mounted by Durlacher Bros. or Dix's own gallery. The correspondence in this series is mostly between Durlacher Bros. and Dix, as well as some third party letters. However, there are many letters to and from Askew, and these have been noted in the box and folder list. The subject files include financial statements, biographical information, exhibition catalogs, often containing price lists, lists of works for exhibitions, pricing and insurance purposes, newspaper clippings, and photographs of the artists and their works.
Art dealers -- United States; Artists -- Great Britain; Painters -- Great Britain; Photographic prints; Art dealers; Artists; Painters; Blume, Peter, 1906-1992; Dix, George; Hepworth, Barbara, 1903-1975; Ironside, Robin; Lear, Edward, 1812-1888; Berman, Leonid, 1896-1976; Nicholson, Ben, 1894-1982; Phillips, Marjorie, 1895-1985; Piper, John, 1903-1992; Wright, Joseph, 1734-1797; Durlacher Bros., New York
- Durlacher Bros. Files, 1946-92; Series I; .4; 1 box
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Correspondence of George Dix
      - Askew, R. Kirk, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University Dept. of Art and Archaeology, 1959, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Other Correspondence, 1950-56, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Third Party Correspondence
      - Keynes, Geoffrey to Michael Ayrton, 1962 Sep 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SUBJECT FILES
    - "British Pictures (Check-list)", 1946-53, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes: Biographical information and lists of works by various artists, and exhibition catalogs from the Anglo French Art Centre, the Arts Club of Chicago and The Manor House
    - Durlacher Bros. "The Work of Samuel Palmer, A Loan Exhibition," exhibition catalog, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Other files, 1959-61, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - "Paintings for Sale"
      - Photographs of works by Eugène Delacroix, William Etty, Henry Fuseli, and Leonid (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Photographs of works by Giuseppe Ruopolo, Charles Swagers[?], Pavel Tchelitchew, and an unidentified work (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Pictures Submitted for Approval"
      - Photographs of works by William Etty, Joseph Wright of Derby, and two unidentified works (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Sold Drawings"
      - Photographs of works by Giuseppe Galli da Bibiena, Edward Calvert, George Chinnery, Eugène Delacroix, and Victoria Dubourg (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Photographs of works by William Etty, Thomas Gainsborough, Théodore Géricault, Philips Koninck, and Samuel Palmer (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Photographs of works by Odilon Redon, Francesco Rognin, George Romney, James McNeill Whistler, and Francesco Zugno (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Photographs of unidentified works, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "Sold Paintings"
      - Photographs of works by Charles Edward Conder, J. Couture, Francis Danby, and Pier Leone Ghezzi (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Photographs of works by William Etty and Edward Lear (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Photographs of works by John Martin (1789-1854), Samuel Palmer (1801-1881), Marco Pino, Salvatore Rosa, Henry Tresham, and Juan Vanderhamen y Leon (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Photographs of works by James McNeill Whistler, Matthias Withoos, and Joseph Wright of Derby (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Photographs of unidentified works, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous photographs
      - Photographs of works by Michael Ayrton and Francis Bacon (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Photographs of works by William Blake, Johann Georg Böhn, Robert Colquhoun, Vincent van Gogh, and Barbara Hepworth (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Photographs of works by Ivon Hitchens, Paul Klee, Edward Lear, Philippe Lejeune, Robert MacBryde, and Titina Maselli (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Photographs of works by John Minton, Henry Moore, and James Mortimer (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Photographs of works by Paul Nash, Palio, Samuel Palmer, I. Rice Pereira, Paul Resika, Ceri Richards, and Leonard Rosoman (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Photographs of works by Bill Sawyer, Ira Schwartz, William Scott, George Tooker, and Bryan Wynter (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Photographs of unidentified works, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Artists Files, 1947-67; Series II; 1.9; 5 boxes
  - BLUME, PETER
    - Subject Files
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1958-64 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Photographs of Peter Blume, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Other files, 1964, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - FRY, ANTHONY
    - Subject Files
      - Photographs of works by Fry, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - GRUNBAUM, JAMES
    - Correspondence
      - Grunbaum, James, 1959, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 33)
        Includes: Correspondence with R. Kirk Askew
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with James Grunbaum, 1953-59 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Photographs of works by Grunbaum, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - HEPWORTH, BARBARA
    - Correspondence
      - Hepworth, Barbara, 1948-59, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
      - Lefevre Gallery, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Perls, Frank, 1950 Mar 7 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Other correspondence, 1949, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Subject Files
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Exhibition Catalogs, 1951-52, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Lists of works, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Other files, 1954, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - IRONSIDE, ROBIN
    - Correspondence
      - A.F R.W. Tweedie, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Bachrach, Samuel, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Baker, Walter C., 1966 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Belding, Eleanor, 1966-67 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Hofer, Philip, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Hubbard, Caryl
        Related Archival Materials note
        See: New Art Centre, Box 2, folders 60-62
      - Ironside, Robin, 1951-65, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 51-57)
      - Laughlin, Ann
        See: Laughlin, James, Box 2, folder 58
      - Laughlin, James, 1966-67 (Box 2, Folder 58)
        Includes: Letters from Ann Laughlin, 1967
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 59)
        Includes: Letter from the Museum to the New Art Centre
      - New Art Centre (London), 1966-67 (Box 2, Folder 60-62)
        Includes: Letters from Caryl Hubbard
      - Saltonstall, Nathaniel, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Worcester Art Museum, 1966 Apr 27 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - Other correspondence, 1965-66 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Subject Files
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1952-64 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Lists of works by Ironside, 1957, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Photographs of works by Ironside, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Other files, 1957-66, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - LEAR, EDWARD
    - Correspondence
      - Fry, Charles, 1947 Nov 29 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - Gimpel Fils, 1947 Dec 23 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - McCord, David [Thompson Watson?], 1947 Dec 9 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Nan Kivell, Rex, 1947 Dec 22 (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - Sargent, Hugh W., [n.y.] Dec 5 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - Other correspondence, 1947-48 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Subject Files
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - Photographs of works by Lear, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Other files, 1947-52, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - LEONID
    Also known as Leonid Berman
    - Correspondence
      Durlacher Bros. Correspondence
      - Cosmopolitan Club (New York, N.Y.), 1964 Nov 5
      - Leonid, 1959-64, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Martin Secker Warburg Limited, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Suffolk Museum, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 83)
        Includes: Letters from the Museum to Leonid
      - Other correspondence, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 84)
      - Third-Party Correspondence
        - Random House (Firm). Correspondence with Leonid, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 85)
          Includes: Letter to Robert Isaacson, Durlacher Bros.
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with Leonid, 1948-66 (Box 3, Folder 86-88)
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 89)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1953-65 (Box 3, Folder 90)
      - Lists of works by Leonid, 1962, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 91)
      - Other files, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - LUBITCH, OSSIP
    - Subject Files
      - Photographs of works by Lubitch, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - MASELLI, TITINA
    - Correspondence
      - Maselli, Titina, 1953-65, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with Titina Maselli, 1953-57 (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - Exhibition catalogs, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 97)
      - Photographs of Maselli, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 98)
      - Photographs of works by Maselli, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 99-100)
      - Unidentified photographs, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - Other files, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - MCEWEN, RORY
    - Correspondence
      - McEwen, Romana, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - McEwen, Rory, 1962-66, n.d (Box 3, Folder 104-106)
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with Rory McEwen, 1962-66 (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 108)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1962-65 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - Lists of works by McEwen, 1962, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 110)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1962-66, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 111-112)
      - Photographs of works by McEwen, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 113-115)
      - Other Files, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - NICHOLSON, BEN
    - Correspondence
      - André Emmerich Gallery, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 117)
        Includes: Letter from André Emmerich
      - Emmerich, André
        See: André Emmerich Gallery, Box 4, folder 117
      - Frankfurter, Alfred M.
        See: Lund Humphries, Box 4, folder 120
      - Gimpel Fils, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 118)
      - Lefevre Gallery, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 119)
      - Lund Humphries, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 120)
        Includes: Letters from Alfred M. Frankfurter to Lund Humphries
      - Miller, Dorothy Canning
        See: Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), Box 4, folder 121
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 121)
        Includes: Letter from Dorothy Canning Miller
      - Nicholson, Ben, 1948-67, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 122-134)
        Includes: Photographs of works by Tom Early
      - Tunnard, Christopher, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 135)
        Includes: Letter from Ben Nicholson to Tunnard, [n.y.] May 30
      - Other correspondence, 1949-59 (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - Third Party Correspondence
        - American British Art Gallery, [n.y.] Oct 16 (Box 4, Folder 137)
          Includes: Letter by Ala Story
    - Subject Files
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 138)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1947-56, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 139-141)
      - Lists of works by Nicholson, 1949-55, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 142-143)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1949-58, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 144)
      - Photograph of Nicholson, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 145)
      - Photograph of an unidentified man, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 146)
      - Photographs of works by Nicholson, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 147-150)
      - Photographs of works by Wilhelmina Barns-Graham, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 151)
      - Other files, 1949, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - NOLAN, SIDNEY
    - Subject Files
      - Photographs of works by Nolan, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 153-157)
  - PHILLIPS, MARJORIE
    - Correspondence
      - Phillips, Marjorie, 1956-67 (Box 5, Folder 158)
      - Phillips Gallery, 1959 Nov 11 (Box 5, Folder 159)
      - Phillips Properties, 1957 Mar 22 (Box 5, Folder 160)
      - Pulitzer, Joseph (1913-), 1956 Apr 30 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with Marjorie Phillips, 1952-59 (Box 5, Folder 162)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1952-59 (Box 5, Folder 163)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1956-59 (Box 5, Folder 164)
      - Other files, 1959, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - PIPER, JOHN
    - Correspondence
      - Donald Morris Gallery, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 166)
      - H.W. Wilson Company, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 167)
      - Piper, John, 1954-67 (Box 5, Folder 168-170)
      - Piper, Myfanwy, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 171)
      - University of Rochester. Memorial Art Gallery, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 172)
      - Other correspondence, 1960-62 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Subject Files
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 174)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1957-61, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 175)
      - Lists of works by Piper, 1955-67, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 176)
      - Photographs of works by Piper, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 177)
      - The Sunday Times (London, England), Colour Section. Issue on Coventry Cathedral, 1962 May 20
      - Other files, 1957-62, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - REYNOLDS, ALAN
    - Subject Files
      - Photographs of works by Reynolds, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 179-180)
      - Other files, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - SCHWARTZ, IRA
    - Correspondence
      - Schwartz, Ira, 1954, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with Ira Schwartz, 1954-58 (Box 5, Folder 183)
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 184)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 185)
      - Other files, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - STUEMPFIG, WALTER
    - Correspondence
      - Ballard, Spahr, Andrews Ingersoll, 1961-63 (Box 5, Folder 187)
        Includes: Letters from R. Kirk Askew
        Includes: Letters from the United States Internal Revenue Service
      - Fifth Avenue Gallery, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 188)
        Includes: Letters from Bror Utter
      - Fort Worth Art Center, 1962 Jun 22 (Box 5, Folder 189)
      - Shea Company, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 190)
      - Stuempfig, Walter, 1960-62, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 191)
      - United State Internal Revenue Service
        See: Ballard, Spahr, Andrews & Ingersoll, Box 5, folder 187
      - Utter, Bror
        See: Fifth Avenue Gallery, Box 5, folder 188
      - Other correspondence, 1959-61 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Subject files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with Walter Stuempfig, 1959-63 (Box 5, Folder 193)
      - Lists of works by Stuempfig, 1962, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 194)
      - Other files, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - TCHELITCHEW, PAVEL
    - Correspondence
      - Tchelitchew, Pavel, 1950-56 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - VAUGHAN, KEITH
    - Subject Files
      - Photographs of works by Vaughan, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 197-199)
  - JOSEPH WRIGHT OF DERBY (1734-1797)
    - Correspondence
      - Bolton and Fairhead, Ltd., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 200)
      - Bouverie, David Pleydell, 1960 Feb 1 (Box 6, Folder 201)
      - Buckley, Charles E.
        See: Currier Gallery of Art, Box 6, folder 203
      - Crombie, Theodore, 1960 Apr 21 (Box 6, Folder 202)
        Includes: Letter to R. Kirk Askew
        Includes: Photograph of Wright's "Indian Window," and copy of article by Crombie in "Apollo," October 1959
      - Currier Gallery of Art, 1959-60 (Box 6, Folder 203)
        Includes: Letters from Charles E. Buckley
      - Federal Insurance Company, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 204)
      - Smith College Museum of Art, 1959-60 (Box 6, Folder 205)
        Includes: Catalog for an exhibition of Wright at Smith College, 1955
      - Vancouver Art Gallery, 1959-60 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Subject Files
      - Durlacher Bros. "Joseph Wright of Derby, 1734-1797, a Loan Exhibition," proofs[?], corrected, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 207)
      - Lists of works by Wright, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 208)
      - Photographs of works by Wright, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 209-211)
      - Rosenblum, Robert. "Joseph Wright of Derby: Gothick Realist," typescript article, corrected, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 212)
      - Rosenblum, Robert. "The Origin of Painting: A Problem in the Iconography of Romantic Classicism," typescript excerpt, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 213)
      - Wedgwood, Josiah. Typescript copies of letters to Thomas Bentley, 1778, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 214)
      - Wright, Joseph. Typescript copy of letter to William Hayley, 3 Dec. 1783, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 215)
      - Wright, Joseph. Typescript copies of letters to Josiah Wedgwood, 1782-89, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 216)
      - Other files, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - ZVER, JAMES
    - Correspondence
      - Hunter College. Letter of recommendation by Dix, 1966 Apr 20 (Box 6, Folder 218)
      - Zver, James, 1966, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 219)
      - Unidentified. Letters of recommendation by Dix, 1965 Dec 22 (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Subject Files
      - Account of Durlacher Bros. with James Zver, 1965-67 (Box 6, Folder 221)
      - Biographical information, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 222)
      - Exhibition catalogs, 1966, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 223)
      - Lists of works by Zver, 1965, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 224)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 225)
      - Other files, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 226)
- Oversize, .8; 1 box
  - Lear, Edward. Other files (in Series II) (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Nicholson, Ben. Other correspondence (in Series II), 1949-59 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Piper, John. The Sunday Times (in Series II), 1962 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Wright, Joseph. Photographs of works by Wright (in Series II), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 230)
- Restricted Fragile, .4; 1 box
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Box 2, folder 31 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Box 2, folder 37 (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Box 2, folder 40 (Box 8, Folder 234)
  - Box 2, folder 41 (Box 8, Folder 235)
  - Box 2, folder 42 (Box 8, Folder 236)
  - Box 2, folder 44 (Box 8, Folder 237)
  - Box 2, folder 47 (Box 8, Folder 238)
  - Box 2, folder 49 (Box 8, Folder 239)
  - Box 2, folder 50 (Box 8, Folder 240)
  - Box 2, folder 51 (Box 8, Folder 241)
  - Box 2, folder 52 (Box 8, Folder 242)
  - Box 2, folder 58 (Box 8, Folder 243)
  - Box 2, folder 59 (Box 8, Folder 244)
  - Box 2, folder 60 (Box 8, Folder 245)
  - Box 2, folder 61 (Box 8, Folder 246)
  - Box 2, folder 62 (Box 8, Folder 247)
  - Box 2, folder 63 (Box 8, Folder 248)
  - Box 2, folder 65 (Box 8, Folder 249)
  - Box 2, folder 68 (Box 8, Folder 250)
  - Box 2, folder 70 (Box 8, Folder 251)
  - Box 2, folder 76 (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - Box 2, folder 79 (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Box 3, folder 86 (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Box 3, folder 88 (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Box 3, folder 91 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Box 3, folder 92 (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Box 3, folder 94 (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Box 3, folder 106 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Box 3, folder 107 (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Box 3, folder 111 (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Box 3, folder 112 (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Box 4, folder 122 (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Box 4, folder 123 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Box 4, folder 124 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Box 4, folder 125 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Box 4, folder 126 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Box 4, folder 127 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Box 4, folder 131 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Box 4, folder 138 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Box 4, folder 143 (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Box 4, folder 144 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Box 5, folder 158 (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Box 5, folder 161 (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Box 5, folder 162 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Box 5, folder 164 (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Box 5, folder 166 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Box 5, folder 168 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Box 5, folder 169 (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Box 5, folder 170 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Box 5, folder 171 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Box 5, folder 176 (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Box 5, folder 182 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Box 5, folder 196 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Box 6, folder 200 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Box 6, folder 207 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Box 6, folder 217 (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Box 6, folder 218 (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Box 6, folder 219 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Box 6, folder 221 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Box 6, folder 225 (Box 8, Folder 291)